<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Assembly on Praxis Manual</title>
    <link>/assembly/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Assembly on Praxis Manual</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 15:06:08 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/assembly/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Producing Assembly</title>
      <link>/assembly/producing-assembly/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 14:48:26 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/assembly/producing-assembly/index.html</guid>
      <description>To produce an assembly :
Select the assembly from the assembly tree. Praxis displays the assembly parts with their repetition counts in the parts pane.
Use new job command to bring the job dialog.
Adjust the Assembly Count and press OK.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Import Non-Sheet metal Parts</title>
      <link>/assembly/import-non-sheet-metal-parts/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 15:01:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/assembly/import-non-sheet-metal-parts/index.html</guid>
      <description>When an assembly part is imported, Praxis :
Extracts the sheet metal parts and adds them to the Part library.
Separates the non sheet metal components and adds them to the Component library.
Adds the assembly to the assemble library.
If the part was imported earlier as a sheet metal part, it removes them from the part library
The imported assembly BOM contains both components and parts. Selecting an assembly from the assembly tree, shows both parts and components contained inside the assembly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Nests from Assembly</title>
      <link>/assembly/create-nests-from-assembly/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 15:06:08 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/assembly/create-nests-from-assembly/index.html</guid>
      <description>A new assembly can be imported from a CSV file.
Use open • import assemblies… command and select a CSV file to import it as a new assembly. Update the assembly details, quantities or use the Add…/Remove… buttons to update the BOM before importing the assembly and the parts.
Same CSV format used for creating new job can be used for importing new assemblies as well.
Once imported, you can prepare and assign Static Nests to these assemblies.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>