<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Installation on Praxis Manual</title>
    <link>https://endearing-halva-664fec.netlify.app/introduction/installation/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Installation on Praxis Manual</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 15:06:41 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://endearing-halva-664fec.netlify.app/introduction/installation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pre-Requisites</title>
      <link>https://endearing-halva-664fec.netlify.app/introduction/installation/pre-requisites/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 14:15:34 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://endearing-halva-664fec.netlify.app/introduction/installation/pre-requisites/index.html</guid>
      <description>Note Praxis setup displays the below mentioned warning message at the beginning of Installation if the Praxis setup is run without running the Pre-Requisites. Pre-Requisite installation is necessary only for the first time and can be ignored thereafter.
Praxis setup displays the below mentioned warning message at the beginning of Installation if the Praxis setup is run without running the Pre-Requisites. Pre-Requisite installation is necessary only for the first time and can be ignored thereafter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Server/Full Installation</title>
      <link>https://endearing-halva-664fec.netlify.app/introduction/installation/serverfull-installation/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 15:00:21 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://endearing-halva-664fec.netlify.app/introduction/installation/serverfull-installation/index.html</guid>
      <description>Praxis is a distributed, Server/Client application. Select Full installation option on the components selection page to perform the first install.
Check ON Install SQL Express 2019 while installing Praxis on a new machine. This is necessary only for the first time and can be ignored thereafter.
Note SQL Express 2019 installation is needed only for the Server. This option is not available for Client and Sync Installations.
Click Install to begin the Installation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Client Installation</title>
      <link>https://endearing-halva-664fec.netlify.app/introduction/installation/client-installation/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 15:06:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://endearing-halva-664fec.netlify.app/introduction/installation/client-installation/index.html</guid>
      <description>Run Pre-Requisite Installation like Server before beginning the Client setup.
In the client machine, after executing the Installer, Select Client option on the component selection page.
Proceed with the standard installation steps and click Install to proceed with the Installation in Client Machine.
Once installation is completed, Praxis is automatically launched. Provide the Server name or IP address to connect with Praxis server.
Once connected, Praxis displays the Sign up prompt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Praxis Setup Installation</title>
      <link>https://endearing-halva-664fec.netlify.app/introduction/installation/praxis-setup-installation/praxis-setup-installation/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 14:46:47 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://endearing-halva-664fec.netlify.app/introduction/installation/praxis-setup-installation/praxis-setup-installation/index.html</guid>
      <description>Execute Praxis Setup to begin the installation
Choose the installation directory or accept the installation default C:\Program Files\Metamation\Praxis and click Next.
Installation Packages Full Installation – In this mode all components (Server, Desktop and Engine) are installed on the same computer.
Server Installation – Only server and Desktop are installed.
Client Installation – Only Desktop is installed on the target computer. You can also pick Engine in this mode.
Stations – To set up stations for Flux, MetaCAM, RightAngle, Vulcan.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>