<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home Page on Praxis Manual</title>
    <link>/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home Page on Praxis Manual</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 12:31:49 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>/introduction/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 15:06:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/introduction/index.html</guid>
      <description>General Overview Praxis is an MES based Application which handles the complete workflow of production in Shop Floor. It interfaces with all other Flux modules like FluxBend, FluxCut, RA(Bend Control) and Vulcan(LaserControl).
Manages all parts from different customers.
Creates Jobs for the machines according to Orders.
Interacts with FluxBend and FluxCut for you to focus on the creative tasks.
Job with orders is created against customer. Order status can be tracked easily using color code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part Library</title>
      <link>/part-library/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 17:12:50 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/part-library/index.html</guid>
      <description>New parts can be imported and viewed using Part Library page.
The parts are added to the list and are submitted to the Praxis Engine for further processing.
While dropping part in Part Library, it goes throught the following three stages i) Part Import ii) Bend/Fold tooling iii) Cut tooling. First two steps are carried out using Flux core whereas MetaCAM engine (Trek.exe) is used for the third.
In the first stage:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assembly</title>
      <link>/assembly/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 15:06:08 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/assembly/index.html</guid>
      <description>Praxis can import and explode assemblies into Parts and non-sheet metal components. To import assemblies : use open command, choose Import Parts… option and select assembly files in open – file dialog. All Assembly files filter can be used to filter assembly – only files in the file dialog.
Once imported, Praxis displays the assembly list under the assemblies tree in the Part Library. Click on the assemblies toolbar button on the right to switch to this view.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Job</title>
      <link>/job/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 17:37:08 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/job/index.html</guid>
      <description>Praxis uses Jobs to capture and track customer orders. Typically, a job contains a collection of parts with varying quantities, due dates, priority and part order.
New jobs can be xxxxx xxxxx
Imported from spreadsheets(csv, xlsx)
Created from existing parts from the part library
Drop parts directly into jobs page and manually provide job parameters
From Assemblies.
Job View Jobs are displayed in tiles view where each job is displayed with a few basic properties like Job ID, Job reference, Customer name, Total parts etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Job Spread Sheet</title>
      <link>/job-spread-sheet/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 12:18:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/job-spread-sheet/index.html</guid>
      <description>While importing job via spreadsheet for the first time, Praxis displays the Spreadsheet Mapping dialog. Use it to map the Praxis fields to the Spreadsheet columns. The mapping UI displays Praxis fields in the left and the Spreadsheet columns preview in the right top. The Mapping preview is displayed in the bottom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factory Settings</title>
      <link>/factory-settings/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 12:32:55 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/factory-settings/index.html</guid>
      <description>During the installation, Praxis imports CAM machines from Flux and MetaCAM and builds a routing table with possible workflow routes between. A route is a connection between the two processing stations in the routing view.
In this view:
Machines are displayed as processing stations. Each station is drawn with a picture and name.
The stations are connected to each other with routes indicating a feasible workflow path which a part can take from start-to-finish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filters</title>
      <link>/filters/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 16:32:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/filters/index.html</guid>
      <description>It is possible to search parts, jobs and nest based on their tooling status, production feasibility, used punch and bend tools etc. Pre-defined filter choices enhance the filter usability further.
Based on the selected column, the search icon changes to a drop-down button. Clicking this icon (or using Down Arrow keyboard shortcut, when the keyboard caret is on the search-box) brings up the choices dropdown. The dropdown contains list of items which can be selected to quickly apply a filter choice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAD Extensions</title>
      <link>/cad-extensions/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 17:55:13 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/cad-extensions/index.html</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HMIControls</title>
      <link>/hmicontrols/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 15:32:09 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/hmicontrols/index.html</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>