<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Job on Praxis Manual</title>
    <link>/job/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Job on Praxis Manual</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 17:37:08 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/job/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Planning Jobs</title>
      <link>/job/planning-jobs/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 16:18:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/job/planning-jobs/index.html</guid>
      <description>The Job is planned in one of the following ways to extract a higher throughput in lesser work steps.
Mixed mode nesting
Interactive Nesting
Pull Workflow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Job Workflow</title>
      <link>/job/job-workflow/job-workflow/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 15:54:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/job/job-workflow/job-workflow/index.html</guid>
      <description>Create a job From part library Select a single part or in batches and right click to open the new Job command panel.
Choose New Job. The new job dialog pops up with the selected parts.
Job Ref is auto populated whereas Customer, Comments field can be filled in by the user if required.
From the spreadsheet Spreadsheets can be imported by dropping it on the jobs page or using the open • import jobs command.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto Release Job</title>
      <link>/job/auto-release-job/auto-release-job/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 16:17:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/job/auto-release-job/auto-release-job/index.html</guid>
      <description>These nest settings can be used to control the auto-nest behavior in Praxis.
Auto-release packing cut-off: This value is used to decide whether a nested layout is held in approval queue and is renested again when new parts are planned or they are released for production and related outputs are exported to the output folder.
Auto-release due date cut-off: This is not used by auto-nester right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layout Commands</title>
      <link>/job/layout-commands/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 17:36:56 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/job/layout-commands/index.html</guid>
      <description>Send to machine… The layouts are put in the release queue if they fall below the cut-off set via the nest settings. These layouts are retried for nesting when more parts are queued for nesting. The Send to Machine command moves such layouts from in-approval to the released state. Once released, they are no longer retried for repacking and the layout outputs are saved to the machine’s output location.
Add Parts… Use this command to add more parts to a relatively poorly packed layout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nest Output Settings</title>
      <link>/job/nest-output-settings/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 17:37:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/job/nest-output-settings/index.html</guid>
      <description>Use Output settings from factory • settings • job to control the outputs generated by Praxis. The outputs generated are saved at Cut output destination set at factory • settings • cut page. The nest outputs are saved to the individual folders named after the nested layout.
Save layout NC and reports: The NC file is saved to the output folder along with other outputs.
Save layout file: The nested layout along with the layout parts are saved to the output folder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layout Report</title>
      <link>/job/layout-report/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 17:37:05 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/job/layout-report/index.html</guid>
      <description>Praxis saves a html report along with the other outputs. This is a fixed template report, and it contains various estimation and composition details. The reports have multiple sections:
The header section contains the key layout information like the machine, material, runtime, sheet count etc.
This is followed by a layout picture. The layout picture displays parts colored by the nest instance (the job-item). Placing the mouse over the part instance displays basic part details like the Name, Job ID and the Instance#.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of Date Layout</title>
      <link>/job/out-of-date-layout/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 17:37:08 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/job/out-of-date-layout/index.html</guid>
      <description>When a part is imported in Praxis, it checks if a part with same name and content already exists. The import is skipped, if the part already exists and the content (or revision where applicable) is same. The existing content is replaced with the new one if they are different. Praxis also checks if the part is already nested in the active layouts (yet to be produced) or static nests (layouts assigned to Praxis Assemblies).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>