<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Filters on Praxis Manual</title>
    <link>/filters/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Filters on Praxis Manual</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 16:32:23 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/filters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Drop down Command Bar</title>
      <link>/filters/dropdown-command-bar/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 15:15:47 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/filters/dropdown-command-bar/index.html</guid>
      <description>Command Shortcut Description Clear Selection Ctrl + X Unselects all selected choices and refreshes the filter items view. Select Highlighted Ctrl + A Selects all highlighted choices. This command stays disabled if item highlighting is not applicable for the selected field. Apply All &amp;amp; Applies ALL (vs ANY) selected choices to the filter match. Pin In/Out Menu Ctrl + Down/Up When pinned, the dropdown menu stays open even when the current focus moves to another window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part Library Filter</title>
      <link>/filters/part-library-filter/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 15:29:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/filters/part-library-filter/index.html</guid>
      <description>Filtering parts by tooling status Select Tooling Status search field to filter parts by their tooling status. The dropdown displays states as colored checkboxes and machines where White is OK, Orange is Error and Yellow is a Warning state. The Apply All (&amp;amp;) button is enabled in this case to apply the filter condition for all selected machines.
Filter Description Displays parts which have at least one tooling error Displays parts which cannot be cut using TruLaser 3030 machine Cut Infeasible: These parts cannot be cut on any cutting machine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save Filter</title>
      <link>/filters/save-filter/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 16:16:31 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/filters/save-filter/index.html</guid>
      <description>Save Filter by Name Use menu command Save Filter… or shortcut Ctrl+S to Save the filter by name. The Save Filter dialog can also be used to delete pre-existing filters. Selecting from an existing item, overwrites the item with the new filter.
Select saved filters Click on the filter selection menu button from the right-hand-side or use V shortcut key to list and select a saved filter. Select All option to clear filters and list all items.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Job Page Filter</title>
      <link>/filters/job-page-filter/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 16:32:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/filters/job-page-filter/index.html</guid>
      <description>The Jobs search functionality has significantly improved in this build. This makes it easier to locate Jobs, Active Parts and Nests based of various:
Order criteria like the priority, due date, customer, ordered part and quantity etc.
Planning/Scheduling status like the scheduled machines, sheets to-do, sheets completed, nested parts, nested layouts etc.
Nest attributes like nest efficiency, raw-material, unique and total parts, job IDs and counts.
Sample Filters Part/Layout Name The Part name field appears in the Jobs and the Nests page.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>